let quizData = [
    {
        question: "ガ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ギ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "グ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ゲ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ゴ",
        options: ["ga", "gi", "gu", "ge", "go"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "ザ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ジ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ズ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ゼ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ゾ",
        options: ["za", "ji", "zu", "ze", "zo"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "ダ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ヂ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ヅ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "デ",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ド",
        options: ["da", "ji", "zu", "de", "do"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "バ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ビ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "ブ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ベ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ボ",
        options: ["ba", "bi", "bu", "be", "bo"],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "パ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "ピ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "プ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "ペ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "ポ",
        options: ["pa", "pi", "pu", "pe", "po"],
        answer: 5
    }
];